Opening workou two teams locking on ici
broker premier league two two six one and
one team and pink panthers in the counter of
three to one who aaja aaja
ok so pink panthers team are you ready and
one l one team are you ready?
OK before we start in the count of
three to one the National Anthem plays.
Victory to India.
Vande
Kya
Om
Bhai
So Hello and Welcome back once again to the
ICICI Brokers Premier League 2626 It's
time for the Big One, The Grand Finale,
The Final Battle, The Final Encounter, The Final
Titans and the Final Toss time and with me the
two Captains with me Sunny from One One Ill
One Team and with me Hemant Pink from Pink
Panthers, We are the Match Officials Himanshu Sir
and Deepak Sir.  So, who will spin the
coin will Deepak Sir who will call?  The Pink
Panthers Will Call.
Tells is the call
Tells it is you want the toss what you
decided and why will
bowl first
and will
register the opposition team one by one in minimum runs
ok I wish you all the best and Sunny sir 10
overs game correct 10 overs game so it will be
like 100 plus
I think will target be 160?
160 Will Target.  How Many We Make?
All the best sir.   Thank
you.
OK I wish you all the best.  Let's have a big round of
applause.
So Pink Panthers gave the toss and
decided to bowl first.  They invited one
and one team to bat first.  Stay tuned for
the live action coming up.  And fasten the seat belt.  The
weather is going to be very exciting.
Thank you very much.
Vanakam keva ho namaskaram vandanam bajur
koneva hola hadi Welcome to all,
Namaskar to everyone,
we have covered both national and international here,
Arpit ji, I would
like to welcome all our viewers who have joined
and once the final grand finale of the
ICICI Labord Brokers Premier League
226, we will not start like this,
so in the count of everyone with me right now
10 join me, count down 10, come on eight six five four three two one
and game on, let's have a
big applause, here we
go, first ball,
first over of the spinner, here we will
see a very tough competition of the spinner in the power play.   Yes,
first three overs power play
and we are on strike here.
Excellent bowling here.
Completely surprised the batsman here.   Yes.
Good turn,
Ravindra Jadeja does that turn very well here.
Brad Hawk was there too.
Pushed lightly here and stole a run.
First run inu the account of one all one
team.
We also have to appreciate all the players.   It is
not easy to maintain your stamina while playing so many matches continuously.  And we can see that the
level of intensity has not reduced at all throughout the match.
All the players are giving their best
in the field.
Again very good line bowling.  Bowling a very tight
line,
not giving any room to the batsman here.
Would Bhavesh like to take some fancy chances
here again?  As we have
seen in previous matches.
This time, try to hit a big shot.
This time he has played it quite straightforward.  Looks like a
message has been sent from the Captain this time.   A
little impressed in the beginning.  Good
start, just one run in four balls
and this brilliant shot, ball in the air,
fielder present on the boundary line, will have to be
satisfied with two runs here and here a
little confusion is also seen in
between.  Demand for third run but not available,
third run will also be available here.  Misfielding will prove
costly here and every run will prove costly in the final.   There is
absolutely no scope for mistake here
in the final match,
that game of pressure is like this, some final matches
and
roller coasters,
sometimes something is bound to happen, sometimes something is bound to happen,
five balls, four runs,
no wicket, what a turn in the last ball of this over,
excellent, completely deceived,
excellent start here
by Prateek Kadam, one overs gone, four four, no
loss, one one team,
as Mitesh ji, you told me,
reminds me of Ravindra Jadeja, bowling a
very tight line and very fast spin,
fireworks are
not visible here, the start is
very slow anywhere in the distance, here
I would like to say, considering the finals, a
good start here by the team Pink Panthers
and both the teams have been unbeatable in this entire
tournament, if I am not mistaken in this, yes,
absolutely Mitesh ji, you are right,
starting the second over, Bhavesh is on strike, making
some changes in the field, the
bowler has
one fielder in the area of ​​deep cover and one
in the area of ​​mid-wicket, two fielders outside the third
yard circle, he has pushed lightly, the
fielder at third man has stopped there  Will take.  Good
effort only a single run.   There
could have been two runs if we had taken a chance here, but we did
not take the risk considering the finals.   Of
course, if MS Dhoni and Virat Kohli were
batting, they would have easily taken two runs.
Yes, absolutely, there is no doubt about that.  The
comparison might be a little wrong
here, Ritesh ji.
Very great batsman Virat Kohli MS
Dhoni running the wickets very fast.
Mana Bhesh does wicket keeping but not MSD,
in this over also he is bowling in a very tight lane,
we have not seen any boundary till now,
Mitesh here,
yes absolutely Rahul Sawant, excellent start,
see the way he is bowling,
this time he has released with slow speed, so it is
important with the release point and
variation, you completely
pressure the batsman, you influence him,
absolutely very century bowling, the
first over and the second over also, if we see, he is
coming with complete planning and is
not giving any room to the batsman at all.  Whatever
balls we have seen, they are being bowled wicket to wicket,
whatever length is there, they are being bowled on good length only,
excellent bowling, so because of this I
think after winning the toss, the
decision of bowling was the right decision here by the team Pink
Panthers,
yes absolutely, here Doug Sehgal did
not play his natural game,
swing was missed, looking for a big one, excellent
pitch of delivery from Rahul Sawant
and the power play is
not getting any benefit here, One Allen is
bowling very well by the Pink Panthers, they are
not giving any chance at all,
if you see here, whatever
bowling has been done till now, which we can see on the Wagon Wheel,
here
Arpit ji has drawn the Wagon Wheel.   You did a
great job.  It is very fast, now the
fastest is only Arpit.
This time today I have pushed it with light hands.   Will
take only one run.
Super start.
Four runs came in the first over.  Four runs have come in this over so far.
Eight runs, no wickets.
Rahul Sawant will bowl the last ball of this over.   Let's
check here to see if the over is
over.
Meanwhile, we are giving you updates on the international match, the
series decided match between India vs New Zealand.  The
score given by New Zealand to India was 338. India
chasing here, 25 overs completed,
135 for four. Kohli and Nitish Kumar Reddy
on batting. Kohli still playing on 59.
We will keep giving you this update in between. Do
n't worry,
you will get all the updates related to the ICC Lord Brokers Premier League.
Absolutely, Arpit ji,
Virat Kohli is in our comb and we are Nitish.
Steady start from the team one and one team
in the grand finale of
and this brilliant shot will get a
four here. First boundary of the match
coming. Yes, powerful, brilliant four runs one and one
team, let's have a big applause. First
boundary of the grand finale.
Nine for no loss
now 13 for no loss,
excuse me
14 for no loss. Is
this the start of the big over? Mitesh,
yes, absolutely, they say that everyone's day comes
and now one and one team is trying to hit big shots.
Totally beaten
Mitesh, if you see all the
matches that have happened today, all the batsmen have hit the back
boundary.  Pointing towards the
shorter end of the field, everyone focused a bit on that and lost a
lot of wickets because of that here
and look at the turn and this stump,
excellent stumping gone out, a
very brilliant wicket keeping display
here, it was not easy to catch this ball
and that's MSD beyond the stumps,
first wicket keeper here, One L One team, good
stumping by Rahul 2.3, it's 3 for one,
last match's man of the match Sridhar
going on strike here, one down,
One L One team has a lot of hope from him in the final,
his jersey number is four and will he hit a four on the first ball because
this is what the heart desires, he will
hit a four on the first ball, I am
sure, he
tried his best, the batsman missed here.
Excellent bowling here
by Pink Panthers, if the first ball is left
which is a wide ball, then the bowling is
quite good
and the batsman misses the ball completely while creating room, the
umpire signals 22, will have to be satisfied with just one run,
One L One team
tries to hit another ball and on
appeal for wide, at the
end of three overs only 14 runs
at the loss of one wicket,
very slow start, could
not take advantage of the power play at all, One L One team will have to make a
huge score keeping in
mind the finals,
but their aggressive batsmen are still
on strike.  Sridhar and Bhesh both are on the crease.
Vikas Shukla has
bowled very well here while coming to bowl, he has bowled very well so far in this league
and the field was opening here, at the end of the power play
all the players were set on the boundaries
and he hit the shot in the gap but the fielder was present
and two runs were demanded but a
very good call by Bhesh here
otherwise there was a chance of getting run out.
In the previous matches of One L One team, we saw that there were many run outs
due to confusion which proved to be very costly for the team.  The
match went till the super over.   Yes, it was
absolutely a great match here and
this time he made room
down the leg side for wide, umpire Mr.
Fayaz Sheikh
gave the signal but one on 16
and what kind of wicket keeping is this,
stopping the ball with the waist here
is more dangerous than AI
and this Bhavesh was finally successful and what four runs he
stopped, we will have to see,
Arpit ji is never wrong for four runs.
Yes, we should have waited for the umpire's decision
but the ball had gone outside the boundary line,
so I signaled four runs.   Of course,
here we will definitely wait for confirmation.
3.2
One L One Team
Bhavesh with a four on 20, coming live here,
can he extend his innings?   Yes, it
is definitely the final match.
Keep in mind that many viewers are watching live on YouTube.   Yes, if not now then never.
Tried to hit an ultipillary shot but could
n't time it.  The umpire's signal has to be seen.
Leg bye signal here.
21 for one.
10 overs match The Grand Finale Live from
Fatima Grounds Vidyave Mumbai
and once again under floodlights Arpit ji
and another attempt to hit a big shot and a
very good bowling performance as
seen till now, if we leave aside one or two
shots, we have
not seen many big shots here, should we
go for singles One L1 team,
if they play dot balls too much then they will
not be able to make a big score, more
fireworks should be done now, only two fours till now
in this entire innings, waiting for that
fire wack big six
yes yes fire wack, I am waiting for it since long, it
seems we will see it only after the finals
and one more attempt to hit a helicopter shot here but
only got dust from
there.   The
batsman is trying hard
but the ball is not getting converted here.
After four overs, the One L One team is at 22 and
now it remains to be seen what wonders Bhesh and Sridhar will do in this coming over.  Will you make the
bowler miserable?
And the message from the dugout is that
some attention should be paid to the strike rate of the batsman.
Pink Birds has come here with complete planning,
Mitesh ji, nowadays it is the era of technology.
All the players nowadays come with complete planning.
All the videos are available here.
If you see our YouTube live, the
angles
and camera angles look very good and beautiful in the replay.
I got very good
feedback from the YouTube live here yesterday.
Yes, absolutely modern technology and
with that technology if you
take full advantage of it then it will be a spectacular and
proper broadcasting
and all the players there on
a big screen on YouTube
and there is an opportunity and after four overs only 22 runs, the
run rate of one L1 team is less than six, here
looking at the finals we
would like to say it is very low
and this is a very brilliant shot, a
very good effort there and see this
six,
you said the start was a bit slow
but now a
strong blow here, six runs and we will be looking for this
now, Sridhar and Bhavesh should
bat like this, some fireworks,
28 for one, Hemant the captain
and one more, he hit it backwards.  Fielder
present there.   The
Pink Panthers have already set up their field here,
considering the danger there.
Yes, One L
One team and Pink Panthers have performed very well throughout this
tournament.
So Arpit ji can say best versus
best.   Yes of course.  There
is no doubt in this.  This is a
match of best versus best.   The
matches we saw here were
very intense matches throughout the league.  The
entire team has given their best effort.
So the best team, the best 11,
we are seeing the best 22 players on the ground here.
This time I pushed it lightly.
Going for two runs.  There may be danger.
Direct,
very good running,
ran two runs here,
increasing the run rate here, One L One
team
and tried another big shot,
tried one run here but stopped,
10 runs have come from this over so far, a good
over for One L One team, will try a big hit here,
Bhavesh at 4.532,
Hemant will bowl the last ball of this over
and here in the dugout we can see Prashant getting
ready for the next batting
and after five overs, 33 for One One All One
team,
Prashant going to the ground here
and Bhavesh retired,
now new batsman
as we get to see in modern leagues these days.  There is
no compromise on strike rate here.
But playing in such a big historical ground is not easy,
it is very difficult, there should be strength and delicacy along with strength,
yes one thing has to be noted that Mitesh ji is playing
her first One L One match here
in floodlights, so it can be a challenge for her.   In
yesterday's match, his batting was
not under floodlights.  Fielding was empty.
And there is another short fielder at the back,
where the demand for two will have to be satisfied with one.   There are
already fielders set up there from Pink Stone
because that end
of the boundary is very small.  He does not want to take any kind of risk.
New time Amol Kolte is here
and this time he has sent the ball in the air,
fielder was present and he dropped it
and could take only one run here
which seemed like an easy catch, while dropping it here it
seems the ball got lost somewhere in the lights, it is
not easy to catch a catch in red lights
Mitesh here,
yes absolutely
if Arpit ji was here he would have taken the catch
because there was Feviquick stuck on your hands.
Yes, I was already setting an excuse for the fielders of the One L One team.
Excellent bowling here by Amol.
Not giving Pink Pens a chance at all here.
Whatever binge we have seen so far.
We have not seen any loose delivery here.
Very good bowling yes that's very
good bowling beauty of
delivery no chance for the batter excellent
bowling only three runs given so far in this over
in four balls
excellent wicket keeping here I am
also a fan of Messi, yes yes
here we are getting to see everything
apart from Messi Ronaldo cricket
back to back dot balls three dot balls back
to back two on
536 last ball of this over and a
very good shot of switch hit fielder
present here but four runs
finally successful in hitting switch hit
batsman here
yes Prashant excellent shot and four runs
end of over after six overs two on 40 one IL
one team
slowly increasing the run rate one one
team
what do you think Mitesh you will have to see the score prediction
in the coming overs the way the
presented score looks right now we would
like a little more at 70 here
I believe the score will settle down at 8085.
Yes, for that the ball will have to be sent to the space
constellation, in the kamandal of Lord Brahma,
Sridhar, it is
very important for the batsman to stay here.  If we want to
see a score above 80, then if we want to
make the final exciting, then at least a score of 80 plus is
required here.   Yes, I will
definitely give a challenge.  Now we have to see
in this over.
Going for the second run and will complete the two runs
with acing.
Very good fielding display there.
Generally, Mitesh, what we see is that
big scores are
not made in the big leg finals.  The bowling is tight and the
batsmen do not take any risk in scoring, generally it is a
game of pressure, so that is what happens.
So he says that
such small challenges keep happening in big cities.   Yes,
absolutely, there will be challenges and all the problems, but we will have to
see which government will be there this time, the
government of Pink Panthers or the government of One One team
and here he has hit a very brilliant shot in the air and
wow for these six runs, with this One All
One team completes 50 runs, let there be loud applause
and this run rate keeps increasing, as Mitesh
ji, I told you, Sridhar is
on strike here and is set.
Yes, absolutely another
brilliant shot, fielder present, double
called here and this one is misfielded
[music]
three runs will be given here, two for 53,
proving to be a bit expensive, 13 runs given,
not excellent bowling,
wide ball signaled by the umpire,
proving to be a very expensive over, what is it here, the same
big over,
one more shot going in the same direction, two
called and two runs comfortably, the
running between the wickets that is being seen here by the batsman,
if this was seen in the previous overs as well, then
perhaps the run rate would have been a bit
higher,
I think Arpit ji will be batting next
and six balls, six sixes towards Broad, just
like Yuvraj Singh had hit six sixes, six balls, six
sixes, you have a chance,
I am talking about running between the wickets
and you are talking about six here.   The
score is currently 56 for two. Will bowl the last ball of this over.
Hemant has proved to be a bit expensive.
27 runs conceded 1.5
lightly pushed.  Will have to see with two runs.
Excellent, the fielder has
run there and will take only one run.
If two runs are scored in seven overs at 57 and even 30 runs are scored in the last three overs, then the score will be
close to 90, yes,
definitely close to 90, if the score is made then we will get
to see a very good final match.
Mitesh ji, I think he seems
quite impressed with Rohit Sharma's interview.
In which he had said that people have taken up computers.
Whatever people say sitting in the commentary box does
n't matter to me.   right back at Ya.
They say keep calm and make revolution.
This commentary is for entertainment purposes.  Do
n't pay attention to him.  You have to
focus on your performance.   Yes of course.   To
keep the audience engaged, we have to
use some banter.  So
our live audience is watching on YouTube
from all over India and another shot in the same direction.
Fielder present behind.  Double the demand.   We will have to be
satisfied with one run here.
Yes Prashant will play the anchor role here and
Sridhar will play the strong role.
Sridhar
23 runs in 13 balls and two fireworks, big
hit two sixes
and here there is a very good weather environment,
beautiful ground and beautiful
weather and exciting match
and in this good environment
and it is time for food, so we are waiting that
after this match,
food should be arranged in the commentary box
and this is a very wonderful shot in the air, fielder
present, this time he will not drop that wonderful
catch, here
Sridhar coming back to the dugout after a good
innings,
big applause for Sridhar
23 of 16 with two maximum hits.  There is
no applause at all.  Let there be loud applause.
One and One Team.
Watch Vikas Shukla's Binge Now Arpit Ji
1.48 for one.  Very economical Bing has
economy.  So far, One L1 team has
not played its trump card.  I was waiting for Himanshu ji to
bat here.
Sudhanshu ji has arrived.
So maybe there is a little confusion, there was a
meeting between Sudhanshu ji and Himanshu,
which got cancelled and Sudhanshu ji
went to bat
and this clean bowled,
very brilliant bowling here,
yes Vikas got one wicket and while developing his team
and after eight overs, four for 60, who will
win, who will lose, the
momentum that was created in the seventh over, sorry,
in the sixth over, that again
broke here and the One L1 team will have to pick up the pieces.
Amit, who is an all-rounder, came into bat here and
performed very well
in the last match due to which the match
went into the super over.  He bowls very well.
His batting
is also very good.  So far,
no such good performance has been seen.  Let's hope
he has saved it for the final.
So next two overs coming up of the first
innings 64 for four
and that much needed break because there is water so
tomorrow
and here a small drinks break here of
course
lemon water and mineral water but
here there is no water in the commentary box, no
lemon water, it
is empty the way the
commentary is going on here.  Well,
YouTube doesn't show the faces of the commentators
here.
Mitesh ji, I have received a lot of feedback about
YouTube here yesterday, so I
talked to a lot of people last night which the public is watching.   A
lot of people from Bengaluru and Delhi are watching.
Yes, absolutely
you have been praised a lot here for your
Sher and Shayari and your style of speaking,
you have a good command over regional languages, we got to
see a wonderful commentary
in the entire league, thanks
for all your contribution,
I would like to say many thanks to you
for given the second opportunity,
last year was excellent,
today has become better than that and excellent arrangements have been made, also thank you
to Go Broadcasting
JFSC team, a
big break here, a quick
DRM of five minutes is over,
yes you can see during the adding break,
Pink Panthers team looks quite calm
because they have a lot of control over the match so
far and this is another
wonderful shot
towards covers, fielder is present, we will have to be satisfied with one run.
Currently the score is 4 for 61,
so you will also expect some fireworks,
Arpit
ji, there is no time now, absolutely,
here we will have to take a chance on every ball
and Amit hit the shot very fast on the first ball, the
fielder present there demanded two and two will
not be available, here he
wanted to take another lead but that was
not logged, the lead was
not logged in the system,
4 for 62, score 82, one team
and from the dug out, equal two is being demanded here.
But we will have to manage with single only.
Amit looks very enthusiastic while coming on strike.
63 for four, absolutely everyone's enthusiasm is high here
and after your arrival the enthusiasm has doubled.
So many viewers are also connected to Kolkata.
Arpit ji, while giving feedback from Kolkata,
I would like to tell the people of Kolkata that they should dance a
lot
and in this conversation, along with two, one more
run, three runs have been taken here and four runs have been taken.  What
is the matter.  Very nice, while running here, if you do
n't get a boundary then at least
four runs should be taken by running because we cannot take chances
here,
calories have been burnt right there,
you will have to give electrolyte powder to the batsman now,
all the arrangements have been made, just win the match,
after that you will get everything, if you don't get it then you
can order from Blinket, it
will be delivered on the pitch,
Amit is a very fit batsman, he does not need it, right now
we feel that the Fittest Player of the
Tournament award should also be given.  Amit Arpit ji
ji absolutely
fittest player of the tournament award,
excellent bowling.   The
big shot attempt fails to connect here.
Coming up the last ball of the ninth over 67
for four.  We were expecting 90 but it does
n't seem to be a big score here,
even 75-80 seems difficult,
Mitesh, your prediction seems to be in that line
here,
and one more here, there seems to be a hint of wide, it is
not like that, batting under floodlights is
a big test and
if you play cricket here with a leather ball, it is
not easy under floodlights
and you will have to make do with singles here,
and the
size of the ground, Mitesh ji, if you
see, there is no chance of a
misfield here, two runs are easily scored,
Amit has hit the ball so hard that the
ball broke into two pieces
but did not go out of the boundary line, so the
One L1 team will not get much benefit from it, but a
new ball will definitely come here,
after exactly nine overs, the One L1 team will be four for 70,
so what do you think, you had said 80, will we be
able to cross the 80 mark here,
I had said an ambitious target of 80-85, but
Mitesh ji, your target seems to be correct here.  It was
your prediction
but anything can happen, the last over
is still left, we can get to see two-three big hits
here, yes it is the
last over, the rest of the night is left
and the first ball of the last over is here and he moves
forward and hits the shot, fielder is present there,
demand for two is
easily met here,
Amol Kolte has come to bowl, four on 72,
last five balls and Prashant is playing on 13
with one four in 11 balls, now he will
go for the big hit, he has definitely
given a
big hit, fielder is present here and
drop here
and here there is demand for runs from the dugout
but there are some different conditions on the field so the
batsman will not want to take chances, in the
last four balls, 74 runs were at a
respectable score, so the innings reached here.
And that's gone.  It was a fair delivery
and was he
out? It was an
easy catch there. The
batsman could not take advantage of the full toss ball here and
in the dugout here, before waiting for the umpire's decision, it was
declared a no ball, so there was a
bit of an atmosphere, but a fair
delivery.
Last three balls, a big hit
and from here, a very experienced batsman,
Mr. Puneet, coming on strike, a lot of
expectations from him.
Yes, this time he played in the air. He was going for two runs
and will take two runs here.
76 for five.
Last two balls,
this time over the fielder, but the
ball stuck to his hand and he wanted to play an up and over.
Fall of wicket at number six
and coming off the last ball of the first
innings
of the grand finale, the final match
of the ICSE Lumb Presents
Brokers Premier League Two to Six Season
Three. So it was a great journey, it was a festival
carnival,
yes, absolutely wonderful, the
arrangements here and a very exciting league,
we got to see very good matches here.
So, last ball,
captain on strike
and Sunny ji has said that this is a free hit.
Ball on my hand
And a very brilliant ball in the block hole,
very straight,
so only single run, so 10 overs gone, 77 for
six for one, one team and Pink Panthers need
78 runs to win here, we will have to
see who will be in power.
Yes, Mitesh ji, where do you practice from
?  It seems you have taken full advantage of your two days'
experience.
You made an exact prediction here regarding the target of 75-76.   Yes
absolutely,
many years of experience practicing prediction.
And here in one warning, in the dugout,
using technology,
planning on old matches,
using technology, watching the batting of the Pink Panthers batsman,
okay, so here we will take a small break, see you
after the break, and we have to watch the Pink Panthers
match, they will win here, the One L One team will
defend this match,
and a small break of 10 minutes,
10 minutes break here, stay tuned, so what a
good start from Pink
Panthers, one over 12 runs, welcome back once again to
all the viewers and spectators watching us
live, Myself Mitesh Solanki, welcoming you all, the
grand finale
of the ICICI presenting Brokers Premier
League 226 season three,
in the first innings, here the One L One team has made six runs in
10 overs, 77, and Pink Panthers have started already one over
12 runs, so Arpit ji,
welcome, and once again one over 12 runs,
Pink Panthers have started for that glittering trophy,
yes Mitesh ji, absolutely a very good start  I
will say that bowling is the momentum of bowling.
Maintaining their batting here,
Pink Panthers are
taking full advantage of the power play here and the
run rate at which they are batting
and the runners are present here, so they will definitely
want to take advantage in running.  Converting singles into doubles will
definitely be an advantage there.
Arrangements for water have been made here in the commentary box.
Thanks for the
arrangements.
And another good shot in the backward direction and
here it is an easy
boundary check. We will wait for the
umpire's decision. We
get three runs here, if not four then three.
One run is definitely left here. Every
run is very crucial for our team in the final.
Mitesh ji,
yes absolutely, every run counts.
Single here. Good start here.
Pratik Kadam and Vishram Sakkare have
batted brilliantly since the beginning of this
tournament.
Yes, in the entire league, if we look at it, they have
batted very aggressively and
their experience is showing.
Taking full advantage of the field placement here in the power play,
look at this ultiplier shot, but the fielder has
stopped it here and the second run was run quickly. Very
good run rates. While batting here,
Pink Panthers,
Puneet to Pratik
and this time they have made space and played the ball, it is going
out of the boundary line. Four runs by turning the ultiplier.
Wow, wow,
Mitesh ji, the fireworks we were waiting for, is
this the same fireworks? Yes,
absolutely, in
modern day cricket, you will get to see something like this
and one  And a great shot,
what a thing,
excellent batting, so beautiful, so well-wishing
and just looking like
wow,
27 runs have been scored after two overs.
Very strong batting here
by the Pink Panthers, moving ahead with a run rate of 13.5,
taking full advantage of the power play and taking the one-sided match to the finals,
yes, this match has to be won with a run rate of just 6.38.
And here
Mr. Amit Shen One of One L1 team, who is
called the crisis saviour batsman and bowler coming on the board, would he
like to turn the game around by taking a wicket in this over? Yes, we will have to
see, he will definitely do something amazing here.
This will be a dramatic over, definitely it is either
R or Par. Yes, it is
R or Par, we will have to see whose
rule is it. He has
scooped it well. The ball is going towards fine leg. It is going
outside the boundary line. A
very good shot for four runs on the first ball. Here,
Nitesh ji is not able to catch the momentum of the bowler.
If a four is hit on the first ball, then the
bowlers have to make a lot of changes in their plans.   The
score is moving at a very fast pace,
yes it is easy for the Pink Panthers to
win the match because look at the required runs,
six runs and 47 balls and 47 runs,
seeing his bowling reminds me of Daniel Buttler.
Yes,
Neil Batori was a very clever bowler
and this wicket fell as I had
already told you Mitesh ji,
something dramatic will definitely be seen in this over,
despite the first four being hit, a wicket was
seen here, the
ball was placed in the hands of Puneet ji
as if a Motichoor laddu was placed in his hands,
see this, there was a
very happy atmosphere in the dugout of the L1 team
because of the way the runs were coming.  It seemed
that the Pink Panthers were in a hurry for dinner.
But here the wicket has fallen.  So
definitely there will be some slowdown in the pace of runs here.
And here Amit is putting psychological pressure
on the batsman and making a plan
with the wicketkeeper,
yes now while checking the ball the new batsman Rahul Sawant,
what does he check, Mitesh ji
can you explain to me what does ball checking
mean here, how much will the ball bounce, how will the ball fall,
how will it land on the bat,
all this is checked,
thank you Mitesh ji and here coming on the first ball, a
brilliant shot, as soon as
four runs are scored, a powerful brilliant four on the first ball,
see it has become very easy to win this match for
Pink Panthers,
now see the required run rate under six is
5.86 and see the current 13.13,
heavy roller was used before this match.  There is
less bounce in the pitch.   The
ball was very low and the batsman
easily directed it.
Yes absolutely and we had ordered the pitch heavy roller
from Australia.   Yes of course.
DRS equipment
was ordered from England but it got stuck at the port because some
reasons could not clear the shipment.
DRS will definitely be seen in the next season.   At
present, good batting is going on here.
Pink Panthers
42 runs in 7.1 overs.   We
just have to see who gets the winning shiny trophy.
Power play ends easily, here
three overs are at 37, they have done the job,
60%, 70% of the
work is done,
runs have come here at a run rate of 12,
runs have fallen at a very fast pace, they have used the power play
very well, if
we compare the same to same conditions, which was the
batting of the One L One team, they were far behind, the
One L One team here, the
field placement is open, here they are
setting the fielders on the boundaries
and what new bowlers will we get to see
in the final, Akash, he has
not bowled yet in the entire tournament, can he
prove to be a trump card,
Pink Panthers would definitely
not have planned about him because he has
not bowled yet in the entire tournament.
As Mitesh ji, I told you earlier also that
terms card is very much present in One L One
team.  Now you will get to see it.
So bring us your trump card.
Trump cards are available here in bowling.
You can see it
but more than the trump card
we would like to be interested in the mystery box
and this is the first ball in the air and this is a brilliant
six here,
excellent shot six runs,
excellent timing, will take
some time, he has
hit,
wow, a
very brilliant shot here, it is not easy to
hit a six like this here on such a
ball,
absolutely Pratik Kadam,
now he says, keep moving forward, go towards victory,
these steps are not moving, it
seems they are running and another brilliant shot,
this time he will take one run,
I think the commentator has made cuts here, another
bowler will take some time to settle,
fielder is present there, one run is being scored, yes the
power play is over but it does not seem so,
looking at the run rate, the
momentum has been maintained here, Pink
Panthers
now see, only 33 runs
and just these five big hits for each step,
displaying very sensible batting,
giving respect to a good ball
here, the batsman
playing with maturity here,
giving respect to a good ball a
little here, we will also add the Sanskrit word
Mitesh ji, would you like to send a message to the Pink Panthers team,
dinner arrangements by night  It has been
extended till 10:30, the extended
approval has come,
he is showing that hurry and another
brilliant shot here
and the bun is sent straight into space
for six runs,
it's a 100 meter six, yes,
give him 12 runs, not six, yes,
runs are already less here, I would like to be
given only six runs, please
give only six runs here,
27 runs are needed now,
what a hit has Prateek Kadam done in 37-33 balls, wow,
that debut bowler is not being allowed to settle
here, batting very well
here,
yes Mitesh ji, now you will definitely tell me, you had
said that this is the trump card, if you
see MS Dhoni's first match, he also got
out on zero, it is not necessary that it is the first match, a
chance will be given,
someone first becomes a hero, later becomes a
zero or first someone becomes a zero and then a hero,
this is the game of life, in a moment, Tola,
in a moment, Masha, so four gone 51 for one and they need only
27 runs
to lift the trophy, as per the
run rate going on, it seems  The match will be over in two overs,
experienced man of the match of the last match Sridhar,
coming to bowl here, will he be
able to do something,
short pitch ball, very nice, here the
indication of no ball is like icing on the
cake,
what are we seeing here,
Mitesh ji,
this is a gift, a gift even after the New Year,
five runs will be available here, there
should have been four players inside three.   Please
pay attention to such small mistakes.
This Mitesh ji can prove to be very heavy in the final match.
And another brilliant shot, fielder
present here.  We will have to see what a
great powerful hit for six runs Rahul Sawant is also
not far behind after Pratik Kadam Rahul Sawant
said why should I stay behind come we will also
join you
yes absolutely a very spectacular fireworks we are going to see
16 runs are needed now to win the match
yes let's check if he has booked a train for 9:00 o'clock that is why the
batting is going on at such a fast pace here
yes absolutely the
ticket is booked but before that we
would like to check the bat whether it is Ricky Bond's bat from
yes just like the ball is being checked the bat should also be
checked
absolutely right here
this time they are totally beaten
16 runs two big hits and four that's it yes
absolutely I had already told you
this target should be chased within two overs
as per the run rate but the
Pink Panthers seem to be in a hurry here
yes absolutely it is time for lunch it is
time for lunch tomorrow is Monday everyone has to go to
office so everyone wants to take rest for that too
helicopter shot MS D for you
one run
here the batsman would also catch the ball  Have been
cooperating.  He is friendly.
Yes, he is very friendly.  We can see
here the kind of hard hitting he has done in his batting.
Another brilliant shot, fielder present here.
No man's land.
Easily takes two runs.
But here it seems he will take one run.
Bowling, which was considered to be the strength of the One team, was a little more wide in this match,
indicating an extra run was
reported
and
while defending this,
yes only 13 runs are needed in the next five overs
and I think Arpit ji
also needs 13 runs for a half century.   A
very good partnership is being seen.
Here the batsman in front had the
idea that only 13 runs were required at the non-striker's end for a
half-century.
Batsmen showing teamwork here.   Yes.
Would like to double the win with a win.  Your own
victory and the team's victory.
And everyone wins.
Everyone's support.
Looks like they want to secure the Man of the Match trophy.
50 minutes and one more new
bowler Sagar, he is also making his debut here
and this brilliant shot on the first ball took the boat
across, immediately the batsman
needs seven runs, now it will be the government of Pink Panthers,
two new debut bowlers were seen here.
We definitely want to see more bowling from him in next year's league.  The team
wants to remain united,
seven runs away from victory and Pratik Kadam is also seven runs away from
his half-century.
And another brilliant shot with a fielder in the same direction.
But he will just keep looking at the ball.  Have reached 49.
16 balls per move four four four six.
Looks like he is following the 9:00 pm deadline very
well, pink banners here,
he has to catch a flight immediately and on top of that the
flight is calling him here, the car is
calling him, the whistle is blowing and only one
run is needed, the score level one run for the
victory and one run for Pratik Kadam to get the
half century,
Amit giving some message here to Sagar,
this reminds me of the time when MS Dhoni
needed 36 runs in seven balls and was
changing the bat.  So, something similar to this,
one more run will be easily obtained and with this the
winner,
Pink Panthers, who were unbeatable in the entire tournament, will be
declared the winner. Now this
tournament is longer than ICI. Proudly
presenting Brokers Premier League 2 and
this winner of 26, Pink
Panthers have now become the winner. With the
runs with which they batted, it seems that they could have easily
chased the target of 160
and they have given this statement
for the next year by Pink Panthers and
I think Mitesh ji, if you can tell me
if I am wrong, because the
batting that we have seen till now is the
best in the entire league, this is the batting done at the run rate,
absolutely correct, here
only 5.3 overs